[
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "New Zealand", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "France", 
      "Switzerland", 
      "Canada"
    ], 
    "question": "In 1893, which country was the first to give women the vote?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Mayflower", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Mary Rose", 
      "The Santa Maria", 
      "HMS Victory"
    ], 
    "question": "Of which ship was Miles Standish captain?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jack Ruby", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mark Bench", 
      "Tom Gunn", 
      "Alvin Grey"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Shot Lee Harvey Oswald, The Assassin Of John F Kennedy?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Khrushchev", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Putin", 
      "Gorbachev", 
      "Lenin"
    ], 
    "question": "In 1953, Stalin Died. Who ultimately succeeded him as the leader of the Soviet Union?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Anthony Blunt", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Frank Johnson", 
      "Christopher Linberg", 
      "Harold Walker"
    ], 
    "question": "In 1979 which English art historian was exposed as a one-time Soviet spy and stripped of his knighthood?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "France", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Italy", 
      "Russia", 
      "Spain"
    ], 
    "question": "Where did the bayonet originate?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "24th December", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "25th December", 
      "26th December", 
      "31st December"
    ], 
    "question": "The Nordic countries (Denmark, Sweden, Norway notably) tend to celebrate Christmas chiefly on which date?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Prime Minister", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Chancellor of the Exchequer", 
      "Minister for War", 
      "Leader of the Opposition"
    ], 
    "question": "What Office Did Churchill Hold For The Longest Continous Period?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Cyprus", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ireland", 
      "Sicily", 
      "Corsica"
    ], 
    "question": "Formed in 1955, with which island was the organisation known by the acronym EOKA associated?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Paris", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "London", 
      "Nanjing", 
      "Amsterdam"
    ], 
    "question": "Which City Did The Allies Liberate On August 25th 1944?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Lord Of The Rings", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Matrix", 
      "The Godfather", 
      "Jurassic Park"
    ], 
    "question": "Peter Jackson Is Responsible For Directing Which Famous Trilogy?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oliver Cromwell", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Henry VIII", 
      "Francis Drake", 
      "Elizabeth I"
    ], 
    "question": "Who banned Christmas in Britain in 1647?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Amelia Earhart ", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Beryl Markham", 
      "Mary Johnson", 
      "Elise Du Pont"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Was The First Woman To Fly Solo Across The Atlantic Ocean? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "India", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Brazil", 
      "China", 
      "Indonesia"
    ], 
    "question": "In what country did \"Sepoy Mutiny\" occur? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Genghis Khan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Timur", 
      "Augustus", 
      "Xerxes"
    ], 
    "question": "What did Temujin change his name to?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Cyprus", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ireland", 
      "Sicily", 
      "Corsica"
    ], 
    "question": "Formed in 1955, with which island was the organisation known by the acronym EOKA associated?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Nine", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "One", 
      "Two", 
      "Six"
    ], 
    "question": "How Many Crusades Were There?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Khrushchev", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Putin", 
      "Gorbachev", 
      "Lenin"
    ], 
    "question": "In 1953, Stalin Died. Who ultimately succeeded him as the leader of the Soviet Union?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Enola Gay", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Big Boy", 
      "Lady Diamond", 
      "Dauntless"
    ], 
    "question": "What was the name of the B-29 used at Hiroshima to drop the bomb?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "President John F. Kennedy", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Lee Harvey Oswald", 
      "John Lennon", 
      "Mahatma Gandhi"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was assassinated on November 22, 1963 in Dallas, Texas?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "1865", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1851", 
      "1832", 
      "1801"
    ], 
    "question": "In What Year Did The American Civil War End?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Catherine Of Aragon", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Anne Boleyn", 
      "Anne Howard", 
      "Catherine Parr"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Was The 1st wife of henry VIII? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oliver Cromwell", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Henry VIII", 
      "Francis Drake", 
      "Elizabeth I"
    ], 
    "question": "Who banned Christmas in Britain in 1647?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Anthony Blunt", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Frank Johnson", 
      "Christopher Linberg", 
      "Harold Walker"
    ], 
    "question": "In 1979 which English art historian was exposed as a one-time Soviet spy and stripped of his knighthood?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Nine", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "One", 
      "Two", 
      "Six"
    ], 
    "question": "How Many Crusades Were There?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Cyprus", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ireland", 
      "Sicily", 
      "Corsica"
    ], 
    "question": "Formed in 1955, with which island was the organisation known by the acronym EOKA associated?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jack Ruby", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mark Bench", 
      "Tom Gunn", 
      "Alvin Grey"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Shot Lee Harvey Oswald, The Assassin Of John F Kennedy?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oklahoma", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Kansas", 
      "Missouri", 
      "California"
    ], 
    "question": "Which US state in 1907 was the last to declare Christmas a legal holiday?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Cuba", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Puerto Rico", 
      "Mexico", 
      "The Bahamas"
    ], 
    "question": "Spain ceded Florida to Britain in exchange for this territory.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Falklands War", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Irish War", 
      "The Vietnam War", 
      "The Gibraltan War"
    ], 
    "question": "Which War Involving The UK Began In 1982?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jim Jones", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "John Jackson", 
      "John Jones", 
      "Jim Jackson"
    ], 
    "question": "Who led 900 followers in a mass suicide in 1979?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Germany", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Switzerland", 
      "Denmark", 
      "France"
    ], 
    "question": "Which country was first to operate an old age pension scheme?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Constantinople", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jerusalem", 
      "Istanbul", 
      "New Constantinople"
    ], 
    "question": "To What Was Byzantium Renamed In 330 AD?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Aqueduct", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Canal", 
      "Forum", 
      "Arena"
    ], 
    "question": "What did the Romans build to convey water? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Tanzania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Uganda", 
      "Zambia", 
      "Kenya"
    ], 
    "question": "Which country did Idi Amin invade in 1979?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jericho", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bagdhad", 
      "Rome", 
      "Damascus"
    ], 
    "question": "Which is the most ancient walled city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Neville Chamberlain", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Winston Churchill", 
      "Anthony Eden", 
      "Clement Atlee"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the British Prime Minister at the outbreak of the Second World War?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Jarrow March", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Swing Riots", 
      "Tolpuddle Martyrs", 
      "The Chartists"
    ], 
    "question": "What famous protest took place in Britain in 1936?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Britain", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "France", 
      "Germany", 
      "China"
    ], 
    "question": "What was the third country to get the atomic bomb?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Franklin Roosevelt", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Dwight Eisenhower", 
      "Lyndon B. Johnson", 
      "Harry Truman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Was President Of The USA At The Outbreak Of World War II?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sandwich Islands", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "James Islands", 
      "Victoria Islands", 
      "Brittania Islands"
    ], 
    "question": "When Cook Discovered The Hawaiian Islands What Did He Name Them?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "1997", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1990", 
      "1982", 
      "1976"
    ], 
    "question": "In what year did the UK's lease on Hong Kong expire?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jack Ruby", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mark Bench", 
      "Tom Gunn", 
      "Alvin Grey"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Shot Lee Harvey Oswald, The Assassin Of John F Kennedy?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Mayflower", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Mary Rose", 
      "The Santa Maria", 
      "HMS Victory"
    ], 
    "question": "Of which ship was Miles Standish captain?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Louis XVI", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Louis XIII", 
      "Charles VIII", 
      "Charles XI"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Was Marie Antoinette's Husband?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Fourteenth", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Twentieth", 
      "Tenth", 
      "Seventh"
    ], 
    "question": "In which century was The Black Death?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ming", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Qin", 
      "Han", 
      "Tang"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Chinese dynasty lasted from 1368 to 1644?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Turkey", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Italy", 
      "Russia", 
      "Spain"
    ], 
    "question": "Germany's WWI allies were Austria-Hungary, Bulgaria, and ________.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Buffalo soldiers", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Traitors", 
      "Picketties", 
      "Kwoquois"
    ], 
    "question": "What name did the indians give the black soldiers that were fighting against them in the late 1800's?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Alaska", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hawaii", 
      "Puerto Rico", 
      "New Mexico"
    ], 
    "question": "In America, what became the 49th state to enter the union in 1959?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "France", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Italy", 
      "China", 
      "Russia"
    ], 
    "question": "Which country blew up a Greenpeace ship in New Zealand?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sandwich Islands", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "James Islands", 
      "Victoria Islands", 
      "Brittania Islands"
    ], 
    "question": "When Cook Discovered The Hawaiian Islands What Did He Name Them?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Italy", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Spain", 
      "Germany", 
      "France"
    ], 
    "question": "What country did the allies invade in World War II's Operation Avalanche? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Germany", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Korea", 
      "Vietnam", 
      "Ireland"
    ], 
    "question": "Which country was split into two zones by the Yalta agreement?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Falklands War", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Irish War", 
      "The Vietnam War", 
      "The Gibraltan War"
    ], 
    "question": "Which War Involving The UK Began In 1982?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Malcolm X", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Martin Luther King", 
      "John F Kennedy", 
      "Lee Harvey Oswald"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was assassinated on Feb. 21, 1965?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Italy", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Spain", 
      "Germany", 
      "France"
    ], 
    "question": "What country did the allies invade in World War II's Operation Avalanche? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Persia\u00a0", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Parthia", 
      "Mesopotamia", 
      "Assyria"
    ], 
    "question": "Prior to 1935 what was Iran known as?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Catherine Of Aragon", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Anne Boleyn", 
      "Anne Howard", 
      "Catherine Parr"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Was The 1st wife of henry VIII? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Mayflower", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Mary Rose", 
      "The Santa Maria", 
      "HMS Victory"
    ], 
    "question": "Of which ship was Miles Standish captain?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Roxana", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Claudia", 
      "Diana", 
      "Helen"
    ], 
    "question": "What was Alexander The Great's wife's name?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Chicago", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Denver", 
      "Dallas", 
      "Seattle"
    ], 
    "question": "The St. Valentine's Day massacre took place in this which city? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Capricorn", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Gemini", 
      "Aries", 
      "Scorpio"
    ], 
    "question": "If you were born on Christmas Day, what would your star sign be?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Chucky", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Freddie Kruger", 
      "Michael Myers", 
      "Leatherface"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Scary Movie Character Has The real name Charles Lee Ray?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Concorde", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Channel Tunnel", 
      "Eurostar", 
      "An animal cloning plant"
    ], 
    "question": "In 1962, for what did Britain and France sign an agreement to build together?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dean Martin", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steve Martin", 
      "Tim Allen", 
      "James Wood"
    ], 
    "question": "Famed as a member of the Rat Pack, who died on Christmas day 1995?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Anthony Blunt", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Frank Johnson", 
      "Christopher Linberg", 
      "Harold Walker"
    ], 
    "question": "In 1979 which English art historian was exposed as a one-time Soviet spy and stripped of his knighthood?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "1985", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1979", 
      "1965", 
      "1950"
    ], 
    "question": "In What Year Did Mikhail Gorbachev Become Leader Of The Soviet Union?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Mayflower", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Mary Rose", 
      "The Santa Maria", 
      "HMS Victory"
    ], 
    "question": "Of which ship was Miles Standish captain?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Nikita Khrushchev ", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Boris Yeltsin", 
      "Vlademir Putin", 
      "Joseph Stalin"
    ], 
    "question": "Who gave John F. Kennedy a dog named Pushinka? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Crete", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Babylon", 
      "Mexico", 
      "Turkey"
    ], 
    "question": "Where were the ancient script of Linear A and Linear B found?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Black Prince", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The White Prince", 
      "The Red Prince", 
      "The Green Prince"
    ], 
    "question": "What was The Eldest Son Of Edward III Better Known As?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Charles II", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Henry VIII", 
      "James II", 
      "Elizabeth I"
    ], 
    "question": "During Which King's Reign Did The Great Fire Of London Occur?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Prime Minister", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Chancellor of the Exchequer", 
      "Minister for War", 
      "Leader of the Opposition"
    ], 
    "question": "What Office Did Churchill Hold For The Longest Continous Period?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harold Wilson", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Clement Atlee", 
      "Anthony Eden", 
      "Margaret Thatcher"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Was The British Prime Minister Between 1964 & 1969?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Robert E.Lee", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ulysses S Grant", 
      "George Armstrong Custer", 
      "William Tecumseh Sherman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Commanded The Confederate Armies During The American Civil War?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Lucitania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Olympic", 
      "Mary Rose", 
      "Mauretania"
    ], 
    "question": "What was name of the Titanic's sister ship?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Jarrow March", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Swing Riots", 
      "Tolpuddle Martyrs", 
      "The Chartists"
    ], 
    "question": "What famous protest took place in Britain in 1936?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Charles I", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Louis XIV", 
      "Louis XVI", 
      "Charles III"
    ], 
    "question": "Which King Wore Two Shirts At His Execution So As Not To Shiver And Appear Frightened?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Chicago", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Denver", 
      "Dallas", 
      "Seattle"
    ], 
    "question": "The St. Valentine's Day massacre took place in this which city? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Tibet", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bhutan", 
      "Nepal", 
      "Mongolia"
    ], 
    "question": "Which country did China invade on Christmas day 1950", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jim Jones", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "John Jackson", 
      "John Jones", 
      "Jim Jackson"
    ], 
    "question": "Who led 900 followers in a mass suicide in 1979?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Anthony Blunt", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Frank Johnson", 
      "Christopher Linberg", 
      "Harold Walker"
    ], 
    "question": "In 1979 which English art historian was exposed as a one-time Soviet spy and stripped of his knighthood?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "France", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Italy", 
      "Russia", 
      "Spain"
    ], 
    "question": "Where did the bayonet originate?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Nine", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "One", 
      "Two", 
      "Six"
    ], 
    "question": "How Many Crusades Were There?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Germany", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Korea", 
      "Vietnam", 
      "Ireland"
    ], 
    "question": "Which country was split into two zones by the Yalta agreement?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oklahoma", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Kansas", 
      "Missouri", 
      "California"
    ], 
    "question": "Which US state in 1907 was the last to declare Christmas a legal holiday?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Geronimo", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Poundmaker", 
      "Sitting Bull", 
      "Sequoyah"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the last of the apache warrior chiefs", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dwight Eisenhower", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Franklin Roosevelt", 
      "Lyndon Johnson", 
      "Jimmy Carter"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was President of the USA from 1953 till 1961?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Nikita Khrushchev ", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Boris Yeltsin", 
      "Vlademir Putin", 
      "Joseph Stalin"
    ], 
    "question": "Who gave John F. Kennedy a dog named Pushinka? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Chicago", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Denver", 
      "Dallas", 
      "Seattle"
    ], 
    "question": "The St. Valentine's Day massacre took place in this which city? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Lord Of The Rings", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Matrix", 
      "The Godfather", 
      "Jurassic Park"
    ], 
    "question": "Peter Jackson Is Responsible For Directing Which Famous Trilogy?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Louis XVI", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Louis XIII", 
      "Charles VIII", 
      "Charles XI"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Was Marie Antoinette's Husband?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jericho", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bagdhad", 
      "Rome", 
      "Damascus"
    ], 
    "question": "Which is the most ancient walled city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "24th December", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "25th December", 
      "26th December", 
      "31st December"
    ], 
    "question": "The Nordic countries (Denmark, Sweden, Norway notably) tend to celebrate Christmas chiefly on which date?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Southampton", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cardiff", 
      "Portsmouth", 
      "Plymouth"
    ], 
    "question": "Where Did The Mayflower Set Sail From In 1620?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "France", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Italy", 
      "China", 
      "Russia"
    ], 
    "question": "Which country blew up a Greenpeace ship in New Zealand?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harold Wilson", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Clement Atlee", 
      "Anthony Eden", 
      "Margaret Thatcher"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Was The British Prime Minister Between 1964 & 1969?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Constantinople", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jerusalem", 
      "Istanbul", 
      "New Constantinople"
    ], 
    "question": "To What Was Byzantium Renamed In 330 AD?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Black", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "White", 
      "Red", 
      "Brown"
    ], 
    "question": "What colour is Santa Claus's belt?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oliver Cromwell", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Henry VIII", 
      "Francis Drake", 
      "Elizabeth I"
    ], 
    "question": "Who banned Christmas in Britain in 1647?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jack Ruby", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mark Bench", 
      "Tom Gunn", 
      "Alvin Grey"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Shot Lee Harvey Oswald, The Assassin Of John F Kennedy?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Amelia Earhart ", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Beryl Markham", 
      "Mary Johnson", 
      "Elise Du Pont"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Was The First Woman To Fly Solo Across The Atlantic Ocean? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "France", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Italy", 
      "China", 
      "Russia"
    ], 
    "question": "Which country blew up a Greenpeace ship in New Zealand?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Amelia Earhart ", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Beryl Markham", 
      "Mary Johnson", 
      "Elise Du Pont"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Was The First Woman To Fly Solo Across The Atlantic Ocean? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "India", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mexico", 
      "China", 
      "Brazil"
    ], 
    "question": "In what country did the \"Sepoy Mutiny\" occur?\"", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Southampton", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cardiff", 
      "Portsmouth", 
      "Plymouth"
    ], 
    "question": "Where Did The Mayflower Set Sail From In 1620?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "John Lennon ", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Malcolm X", 
      "John F Kennedy", 
      "Martin Luther King"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was assassinated on Dec. 8, 1980 in New York City? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harold Wilson", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Clement Atlee", 
      "Anthony Eden", 
      "Margaret Thatcher"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Was The British Prime Minister Between 1964 & 1969?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "1431", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1213", 
      "1390", 
      "1344"
    ], 
    "question": "In Which Year Was Joan Of Arc Burned At The Stake?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Geronimo", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Poundmaker", 
      "Sitting Bull", 
      "Sequoyah"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the last of the apache warrior chiefs", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Decimate", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Havoc", 
      "Mutilate", 
      "Annihilate"
    ], 
    "question": "What Name Was Given To The Practise Of Killing Every Tenth Man In A Mutinous Roman Cohort?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Crimean", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "World War I", 
      "World War II", 
      "Russian Civil War"
    ], 
    "question": "The Charge Of The Light Brigade Occured During Which War", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Genghis Khan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Timur", 
      "Augustus", 
      "Xerxes"
    ], 
    "question": "What did Temujin change his name to?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Lucitania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Olympic", 
      "Mary Rose", 
      "Mauretania"
    ], 
    "question": "What was name of the Titanic's sister ship?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "1997", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1990", 
      "1982", 
      "1976"
    ], 
    "question": "In what year did the UK's lease on Hong Kong expire?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Nine", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "One", 
      "Two", 
      "Six"
    ], 
    "question": "How Many Crusades Were There?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Falklands War", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Irish War", 
      "The Vietnam War", 
      "The Gibraltan War"
    ], 
    "question": "Which War Involving The UK Began In 1982?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Neville Chamberlain", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Winston Churchill", 
      "Anthony Eden", 
      "Clement Atlee"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the British Prime Minister at the outbreak of the Second World War?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Louis XVI", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Louis XIII", 
      "Charles VIII", 
      "Charles XI"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Was Marie Antoinette's Husband?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "1975", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1969", 
      "1980", 
      "1984"
    ], 
    "question": "The war in Vietnam ended with the fall of Saigon in what year?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "1916", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1900", 
      "1945", 
      "1933"
    ], 
    "question": "In What Year Was The Berlin Wall Erected?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Lady Godiva", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Lady Gaga", 
      "Lady Geronimo", 
      "Lady Galebe"
    ], 
    "question": "Who is famous for historically riding naked on horseback through Coventry, England?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sir Francis Drake", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Horatio Nelson", 
      "George Rodney", 
      "John Jervis"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Played Bowls Before Engaging The Spanish Armada?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "1865", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1851", 
      "1832", 
      "1801"
    ], 
    "question": "In What Year Did The American Civil War End?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Romania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Poland", 
      "Bulgaria", 
      "Turkey"
    ], 
    "question": "Germany's allies in WW II were Japan, Italy, Hungary, Bulgaria, Finland, Libya, and _________.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dane Geld", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "War Bond", 
      "Sax Bandeg", 
      "Guerre Levy"
    ], 
    "question": "What Was The 9th Century Tax Levied To Fight The Vikings?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Belgium", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Netherlands", 
      "France", 
      "Scotland"
    ], 
    "question": "In what country is the waterloo battlefield?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Tanzania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Uganda", 
      "Zambia", 
      "Kenya"
    ], 
    "question": "Which country did Idi Amin invade in 1979?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Royal Family", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Kardashians", 
      "The Osmonds", 
      "The Gibbs"
    ], 
    "question": "In 1969 Richard Cawston Made A Documentary For The BBC About Which Famous Family?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "New Zealand", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "France", 
      "Switzerland", 
      "Canada"
    ], 
    "question": "In 1893, which country was the first to give women the vote?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Nine", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "One", 
      "Two", 
      "Six"
    ], 
    "question": "How Many Crusades Were There?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Aqueduct", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Canal", 
      "Forum", 
      "Arena"
    ], 
    "question": "What did the Romans build to convey water? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Crimean", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "World War I", 
      "World War II", 
      "Russian Civil War"
    ], 
    "question": "The Charge Of The Light Brigade Occured During Which War", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Southampton", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cardiff", 
      "Portsmouth", 
      "Plymouth"
    ], 
    "question": "Where Did The Mayflower Set Sail From In 1620?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "1982", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1990", 
      "1971", 
      "1964"
    ], 
    "question": "In Which Year Did The Falklands Conflict Begin?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "William The Conqueror", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Henry VIII", 
      "Victoria", 
      "Albert the Great"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was crowned King of England at Westminster Abbey on Christmas day 1066?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Melmac", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Barnzac", 
      "Tonzac", 
      "Fardac"
    ], 
    "question": "What planet was 'ALF' from?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Catherine Of Aragon", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Anne Boleyn", 
      "Anne Howard", 
      "Catherine Parr"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Was The 1st wife of henry VIII? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Bill Withers", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Michael Jackson", 
      "Luther Vandross", 
      "Marvin Gaye"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Had An 80's Hit With The Song 'Just The Two of Us,'? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "160", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "0", 
      "50", 
      "300"
    ], 
    "question": "Approximately how many children did pharaoh Ramses II father?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Persia\u00a0", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Parthia", 
      "Mesopotamia", 
      "Assyria"
    ], 
    "question": "Prior to 1935 what was Iran known as?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oliver Cromwell", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Henry VIII", 
      "Francis Drake", 
      "Elizabeth I"
    ], 
    "question": "Who banned Christmas in Britain in 1647?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Lady Godiva", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Lady Gaga", 
      "Lady Geronimo", 
      "Lady Galebe"
    ], 
    "question": "Who is famous for historically riding naked on horseback through Coventry, England?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Chucky", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Freddie Kruger", 
      "Michael Myers", 
      "Leatherface"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Scary Movie Character Has The real name Charles Lee Ray?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Khrushchev", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Putin", 
      "Gorbachev", 
      "Lenin"
    ], 
    "question": "In 1953, Stalin Died. Who ultimately succeeded him as the leader of the Soviet Union?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Aristotle", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Plato", 
      "Socrates", 
      "Diogenes"
    ], 
    "question": "Who taught Alexander the Great? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Melmac", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Barnzac", 
      "Tonzac", 
      "Fardac"
    ], 
    "question": "What planet was 'ALF' from?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Catherine Of Aragon", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Anne Boleyn", 
      "Anne Howard", 
      "Catherine Parr"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Was The 1st wife of henry VIII? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Romania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Poland", 
      "Bulgaria", 
      "Turkey"
    ], 
    "question": "Germany's allies in WW II were Japan, Italy, Hungary, Bulgaria, Finland, Libya, and _________.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "1431", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1213", 
      "1390", 
      "1344"
    ], 
    "question": "In Which Year Was Joan Of Arc Burned At The Stake?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Iceni", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Gangani", 
      "Cassi", 
      "Brigantes"
    ], 
    "question": "Of What Tribe Was Boadicea The Head?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "1982", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1990", 
      "1971", 
      "1964"
    ], 
    "question": "In Which Year Did The Falklands Conflict Begin?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jim Jones", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "John Jackson", 
      "John Jones", 
      "Jim Jackson"
    ], 
    "question": "Who led 900 followers in a mass suicide in 1979?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Nikita Khrushchev ", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Boris Yeltsin", 
      "Vlademir Putin", 
      "Joseph Stalin"
    ], 
    "question": "Who gave John F. Kennedy a dog named Pushinka? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Cuba", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Puerto Rico", 
      "Mexico", 
      "The Bahamas"
    ], 
    "question": "Spain ceded Florida to Britain in exchange for this territory.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Falklands War", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Irish War", 
      "The Vietnam War", 
      "The Gibraltan War"
    ], 
    "question": "Which War Involving The UK Began In 1982?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Chucky", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Freddie Kruger", 
      "Michael Myers", 
      "Leatherface"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Scary Movie Character Has The real name Charles Lee Ray?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Malcolm X", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Martin Luther King", 
      "John F Kennedy", 
      "Lee Harvey Oswald"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was assassinated on Feb. 21, 1965?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Jarrow March", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Swing Riots", 
      "Tolpuddle Martyrs", 
      "The Chartists"
    ], 
    "question": "What famous protest took place in Britain in 1936?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Jarrow March", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Swing Riots", 
      "Tolpuddle Martyrs", 
      "The Chartists"
    ], 
    "question": "What famous protest took place in Britain in 1936?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Alaska", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hawaii", 
      "Puerto Rico", 
      "New Mexico"
    ], 
    "question": "In America, what became the 49th state to enter the union in 1959?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Bill Withers", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Michael Jackson", 
      "Luther Vandross", 
      "Marvin Gaye"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Had An 80's Hit With The Song 'Just The Two of Us,'? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Melmac", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Barnzac", 
      "Tonzac", 
      "Fardac"
    ], 
    "question": "What planet was 'ALF' from?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "1533", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1633", 
      "1733", 
      "1433"
    ], 
    "question": "In What Year Was Queen Elizabeth The I Born?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Aristotle", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Plato", 
      "Socrates", 
      "Diogenes"
    ], 
    "question": "Who taught Alexander the Great? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "India", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Brazil", 
      "China", 
      "Indonesia"
    ], 
    "question": "In what country did \"Sepoy Mutiny\" occur? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sandwich Islands", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "James Islands", 
      "Victoria Islands", 
      "Brittania Islands"
    ], 
    "question": "When Cook Discovered The Hawaiian Islands What Did He Name Them?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dallas", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Atlanta", 
      "Austin", 
      "Houston"
    ], 
    "question": "In Which City Was John F Kennedy Assassinated?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Italy", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Spain", 
      "Germany", 
      "France"
    ], 
    "question": "What country did the allies invade in World War II's Operation Avalanche? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Charles II", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Henry VIII", 
      "James II", 
      "Elizabeth I"
    ], 
    "question": "During Which King's Reign Did The Great Fire Of London Occur?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Concorde", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Channel Tunnel", 
      "Eurostar", 
      "An animal cloning plant"
    ], 
    "question": "In 1962, for what did Britain and France sign an agreement to build together?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Alaska", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hawaii", 
      "Puerto Rico", 
      "New Mexico"
    ], 
    "question": "In America, what became the 49th state to enter the union in 1959?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Franklin Roosevelt", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Dwight Eisenhower", 
      "Lyndon B. Johnson", 
      "Harry Truman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Was President Of The USA At The Outbreak Of World War II?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Iceni", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Gangani", 
      "Cassi", 
      "Brigantes"
    ], 
    "question": "Of What Tribe Was Boadicea The Head?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Neville Chamberlain", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Winston Churchill", 
      "Anthony Eden", 
      "Clement Atlee"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the British Prime Minister at the outbreak of the Second World War?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Henry VIII", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "George I", 
      "Henry VI", 
      "Richard III", 
      "Charles II"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the father of Elizabeth I?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Concorde", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Channel Tunnel", 
      "Eurostar", 
      "An animal cloning plant"
    ], 
    "question": "In 1962, for what did Britain and France sign an agreement to build together?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "India", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Brazil", 
      "China", 
      "Indonesia"
    ], 
    "question": "In what country did \"Sepoy Mutiny\" occur? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dallas", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Atlanta", 
      "Austin", 
      "Houston"
    ], 
    "question": "In Which City Was John F Kennedy Assassinated?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Four Years", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "One Year", 
      "Nine Years", 
      "Seven Years"
    ], 
    "question": "How Long Was The American Civil War?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Southampton", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cardiff", 
      "Portsmouth", 
      "Plymouth"
    ], 
    "question": "Where Did The Mayflower Set Sail From In 1620?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Capricorn", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Gemini", 
      "Aries", 
      "Scorpio"
    ], 
    "question": "If you were born on Christmas Day, what would your star sign be?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dean Martin", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steve Martin", 
      "Tim Allen", 
      "James Wood"
    ], 
    "question": "Famed as a member of the Rat Pack, who died on Christmas day 1995?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Raoul", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Pedro", 
      "Mikel", 
      "Sergio"
    ], 
    "question": "What's fidel castro's brother's name? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Rome", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Athens", 
      "Beijing", 
      "Bagdhad"
    ], 
    "question": "What city was founded in 753 BC?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Jarrow March", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Swing Riots", 
      "Tolpuddle Martyrs", 
      "The Chartists"
    ], 
    "question": "What famous protest took place in Britain in 1936?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Auckland", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Christchurch", 
      "Adelaide", 
      "Brisbane"
    ], 
    "question": "In the harbour of which city was the Greenpeace flagship Rainbow Warrior sunk in 1985?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "President John F. Kennedy", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Lee Harvey Oswald", 
      "John Lennon", 
      "Mahatma Gandhi"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was assassinated on November 22, 1963 in Dallas, Texas?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Louis XVI", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Louis XIV", 
      "Charles IX", 
      "Charles XII"
    ], 
    "question": "Which King Was Overthrown As A Result Of The French Revolution?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "1431", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1213", 
      "1390", 
      "1344"
    ], 
    "question": "In Which Year Was Joan Of Arc Burned At The Stake?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Charles II", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Henry VIII", 
      "James II", 
      "Elizabeth I"
    ], 
    "question": "During Which King's Reign Did The Great Fire Of London Occur?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Catherine Of Aragon", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Anne Boleyn", 
      "Anne Howard", 
      "Catherine Parr"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Was The 1st wife of henry VIII? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Southampton", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cardiff", 
      "Portsmouth", 
      "Plymouth"
    ], 
    "question": "Where Did The Mayflower Set Sail From In 1620?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "John Lennon ", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Malcolm X", 
      "John F Kennedy", 
      "Martin Luther King"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was assassinated on Dec. 8, 1980 in New York City? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Concorde", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Channel Tunnel", 
      "Eurostar", 
      "An animal cloning plant"
    ], 
    "question": "In 1962, for what did Britain and France sign an agreement to build together?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Anthony Blunt", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Frank Johnson", 
      "Christopher Linberg", 
      "Harold Walker"
    ], 
    "question": "In 1979 which English art historian was exposed as a one-time Soviet spy and stripped of his knighthood?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Auckland", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Christchurch", 
      "Adelaide", 
      "Brisbane"
    ], 
    "question": "In the harbour of which city was the Greenpeace flagship Rainbow Warrior sunk in 1985?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Raoul", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Pedro", 
      "Mikel", 
      "Sergio"
    ], 
    "question": "What's fidel castro's brother's name? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Raoul", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Pedro", 
      "Mikel", 
      "Sergio"
    ], 
    "question": "What's fidel castro's brother's name? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "1533", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1633", 
      "1733", 
      "1433"
    ], 
    "question": "In What Year Was Queen Elizabeth The I Born?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Buffalo soldiers", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Traitors", 
      "Picketties", 
      "Kwoquois"
    ], 
    "question": "What name did the indians give the black soldiers that were fighting against them in the late 1800's?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Amelia Earhart ", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Beryl Markham", 
      "Mary Johnson", 
      "Elise Du Pont"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Was The First Woman To Fly Solo Across The Atlantic Ocean? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Henry VIII", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "George I", 
      "Henry VI", 
      "Richard III", 
      "Charles II"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the father of Elizabeth I?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "India", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mexico", 
      "China", 
      "Brazil"
    ], 
    "question": "In what country did the \"Sepoy Mutiny\" occur?\"", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Germany", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Switzerland", 
      "Denmark", 
      "France"
    ], 
    "question": "Which country was first to operate an old age pension scheme?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sir Walter Raleigh", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Sir Francis Drake", 
      "James Cook", 
      "Ernest Shackleton"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Brought Back Tobacco And Potatoes From The Americas?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Southampton", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cardiff", 
      "Portsmouth", 
      "Plymouth"
    ], 
    "question": "Where Did The Mayflower Set Sail From In 1620?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Tibet", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bhutan", 
      "Nepal", 
      "Mongolia"
    ], 
    "question": "Which country did China invade on Christmas day 1950", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Belgium", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Netherlands", 
      "France", 
      "Scotland"
    ], 
    "question": "In what country is the waterloo battlefield?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Buffalo soldiers", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Traitors", 
      "Picketties", 
      "Kwoquois"
    ], 
    "question": "What name did the indians give the black soldiers that were fighting against them in the late 1800's?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Germany", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Switzerland", 
      "Denmark", 
      "France"
    ], 
    "question": "Which country was first to operate an old age pension scheme?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Louis XVI", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Louis XIII", 
      "Charles VIII", 
      "Charles XI"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Was Marie Antoinette's Husband?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Rome", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Athens", 
      "Beijing", 
      "Bagdhad"
    ], 
    "question": "What city was founded in 753 BC?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Waterloo", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Trafalgar", 
      "Windsor", 
      "Dover"
    ], 
    "question": "Where was Napoleon defeated?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Alexander the great", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Odysseus", 
      "Romulus", 
      "Remus"
    ], 
    "question": "His wife was Roxana. His horse was Bacephalus. He was ________.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dallas", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Atlanta", 
      "Austin", 
      "Houston"
    ], 
    "question": "In Which City Was John F Kennedy Assassinated?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Yom Kippur war", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Wailing War", 
      "The Khartoum War", 
      "The Hezbollah War"
    ], 
    "question": "Which famous Arab / Israeli war took place in 1973?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Prime Minister", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Chancellor of the Exchequer", 
      "Minister for War", 
      "Leader of the Opposition"
    ], 
    "question": "What Office Did Churchill Hold For The Longest Continous Period?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "India", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Brazil", 
      "China", 
      "Indonesia"
    ], 
    "question": "In what country did \"Sepoy Mutiny\" occur? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Lady Godiva", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Lady Gaga", 
      "Lady Geronimo", 
      "Lady Galebe"
    ], 
    "question": "Who is famous for historically riding naked on horseback through Coventry, England?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Italy", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Spain", 
      "Germany", 
      "France"
    ], 
    "question": "What country did the allies invade in World War II's Operation Avalanche? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dane Geld", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "War Bond", 
      "Sax Bandeg", 
      "Guerre Levy"
    ], 
    "question": "What Was The 9th Century Tax Levied To Fight The Vikings?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hawaii", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Alaska", 
      "Puerto Rico", 
      "New Mexico"
    ], 
    "question": "What Became America's 50th State On August 21st 1959?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Waterloo", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Trafalgar", 
      "Windsor", 
      "Dover"
    ], 
    "question": "Where was Napoleon defeated?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Four Years", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "One Year", 
      "Nine Years", 
      "Seven Years"
    ], 
    "question": "How Long Was The American Civil War?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Southampton", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cardiff", 
      "Portsmouth", 
      "Plymouth"
    ], 
    "question": "Where Did The Mayflower Set Sail From In 1620?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Paris", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "London", 
      "Nanjing", 
      "Amsterdam"
    ], 
    "question": "Which City Did The Allies Liberate On August 25th 1944?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "France", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Italy", 
      "Russia", 
      "Spain"
    ], 
    "question": "Where did the bayonet originate?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harold Wilson", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Clement Atlee", 
      "Anthony Eden", 
      "Margaret Thatcher"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Was The British Prime Minister Between 1964 & 1969?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Yom Kippur war", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Wailing War", 
      "The Khartoum War", 
      "The Hezbollah War"
    ], 
    "question": "Which famous Arab / Israeli war took place in 1973?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hiroshima", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "Osaka", 
      "Nagasaki"
    ], 
    "question": "On What Japanese City Was The First Atomic Bomb Dropped?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sandwich Islands", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "James Islands", 
      "Victoria Islands", 
      "Brittania Islands"
    ], 
    "question": "When Cook Discovered The Hawaiian Islands What Did He Name Them?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Rome", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Athens", 
      "Beijing", 
      "Bagdhad"
    ], 
    "question": "What city was founded in 753 BC?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Concorde", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Channel Tunnel", 
      "Eurostar", 
      "An animal cloning plant"
    ], 
    "question": "In 1962, for what did Britain and France sign an agreement to build together?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hawaii", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Alaska", 
      "Puerto Rico", 
      "New Mexico"
    ], 
    "question": "What Became America's 50th State On August 21st 1959?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "160", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "0", 
      "50", 
      "300"
    ], 
    "question": "Approximately how many children did pharaoh Ramses II father?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Germany", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Korea", 
      "Vietnam", 
      "Ireland"
    ], 
    "question": "Which country was split into two zones by the Yalta agreement?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "John Lennon ", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Malcolm X", 
      "John F Kennedy", 
      "Martin Luther King"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was assassinated on Dec. 8, 1980 in New York City? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Persia\u00a0", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Parthia", 
      "Mesopotamia", 
      "Assyria"
    ], 
    "question": "Prior to 1935 what was Iran known as?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Charles I", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Louis XIV", 
      "Louis XVI", 
      "Charles III"
    ], 
    "question": "Which King Wore Two Shirts At His Execution So As Not To Shiver And Appear Frightened?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Babylon", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Atlantis", 
      "Jerusalem", 
      "Scythia"
    ], 
    "question": "Where were the Hanging Gardens?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "President John F. Kennedy", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Lee Harvey Oswald", 
      "John Lennon", 
      "Mahatma Gandhi"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was assassinated on November 22, 1963 in Dallas, Texas?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Southampton", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cardiff", 
      "Portsmouth", 
      "Plymouth"
    ], 
    "question": "Where Did The Mayflower Set Sail From In 1620?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Submarine", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Torpedo", 
      "TNT", 
      "The Tank"
    ], 
    "question": "Designed By Robert Fulton, Which Weapon Was Tested In The Seine In 1801?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Rome", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Athens", 
      "Beijing", 
      "Bagdhad"
    ], 
    "question": "What city was founded in 753 BC?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Mayflower", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Mary Rose", 
      "The Santa Maria", 
      "HMS Victory"
    ], 
    "question": "Of which ship was Miles Standish captain?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Lord Of The Rings", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Matrix", 
      "The Godfather", 
      "Jurassic Park"
    ], 
    "question": "Peter Jackson Is Responsible For Directing Which Famous Trilogy?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sandwich Islands", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "James Islands", 
      "Victoria Islands", 
      "Brittania Islands"
    ], 
    "question": "When Cook Discovered The Hawaiian Islands What Did He Name Them?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "John Lennon ", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Malcolm X", 
      "John F Kennedy", 
      "Martin Luther King"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was assassinated on Dec. 8, 1980 in New York City? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }
]
